Just as rides on whispered gales
In the ninth the law of stars is written
A pilgrim's flame that won't submit
Pluto cars the bones of fate
Saturn forges Jupiter inflates
Between the cracks of time you stand
Balancing worlds in each hand
Streels of the night sky
Burning in your eyes
Truth dressed in sheds
Change your side
the seas you've touched the world with galaxies skills of the night sky burning in
your eyes truth dressed in shadows wisdom in disguise
You walk the halls of myth untold A balanced keeper, draped in gold
In the sacred law you guard, divine
Your heart's the temple's soul, the shrine
So raise the scale
Let's fight
Thank you very much for watching.
Yo, yo
What's up guys I
Thought I'd like come on one more time because it turns out there was one more
Interesting video
Wanted you guys to check out
Just to check out something. Yeah, good thing. Yeah, you have to like kind of like
Probably have a beyond IV of epilepsy medication for the show
Make sure I have my glasses where my glasses go
Um
Yeah, there's some another interesting video. Yeah, like I loved the one we watched earlier. It was really really good
but uh, the other one was pretty good too, but it's kind of a little bit depressing, but
Guess hear me. Okay
The North fucking knocked over my coffee. I do have some Irish cream, too. I might drink. I don't know
We'll see. Yeah
Everyone hope you drink I had your epilepsy medication
So, I'll wait for people to get in here, but let's have a look
Mmm
Taste the biscuit
Okay, I'll wait for welcome to psyche awakens TV
More than a live stream. It's a gathering in the shadow in the light
We face chaos comedy and the unknown together
With open panels that never shy away from the truth, I am Psyche, your guide through
tarot, prophecy, and the unfiltered clash of voices.
Tonight, we're stepping into the panel verse where allies and trolls alike reveal themselves
in every card turn.
Every word spoken is part of the story.
So stay sharp, stay curious, because once the gates open, anything can happen.
The show is about to begin.
This is Lilith Scorpiana and you're watching Psyche Awakens TV.
Psyche Awakens TV is a portal to the shadows of the soul where truth burns through illusion
and transformation demands courage.
Psyche rips open the veil of the soul, dragging you into the abyss where raw truth claws at
your core and transformation diverges all fear.
It's a relentless plunge into that only the brave emerge reborn.
Enjoy!
You guys ready for this?
All right, then all right players stay up
I think that is up here, you know, he don't still know, you know, he got to show me the respect though.
He will defend Page though. He will defend Page for sure.
You'll defend Page, but you won't defend God.
But why would he defend an Eastern terrorist-minded person in his mind like me, you know?
Why would he not defend Page, shit?
Wait, what did you do when you were like saying I'm like a cute weird
pet?
It's a Canadian thing.
No, no, paid this own site.
Paged on fuck with site like that.
No, she does not.
Yeah, she's just over there.
There we go.
I love that thing.
Thank you for defending somebody, but it's got to be a Canadian like you.
Let's see. I didn't figure it out what people are saying right now. I didn't defend
paint for everybody, whether it's right or wrong. Not getting the same treatment. I'm
getting. I will defend her before you need to defend her. I def on treatment.
Does she get the AI songs that I got I always defend my fucking page page knows how to I'd know her way better than you
Actually, not the AI songs right and to be fair, you know, there is the page
Will you fall in love with me? And it's you know, it's Alex McQueen. I mean
Page was a good sport
Me and Paige were the people that fucking
Fought hard for fucking psyche harder than you would ever fucking imagine
But imagine this when I tell you
Canadians will always stick together. It's almost like the same breed like fucking Jewish people. They do the same thing
These everybody just stand up who gives a fuck where you're from stopping neutral
If you're on the panel and you're silent, people are going to press you.
Christine has a fucking right to, I have a right to.
We're going to be like, why were you so quiet?
And why are you not quiet when it comes to you?
And your honor and other fucking, we are going to press you.
What was I on the panel for exactly?
I don't want to remind you again, you were mad at Saiki for what?
For something Spunky said and he allowed, didn't it happen?
But that he did because of something Spiky said.
What happened? I squashed it and I fucking like threw it in the trash can like it was over.
Now you can do the same thing for fucking Christine and me be like, you know what?
That's just sounds like bullshit. Saiki, I care about you. I'm here to support you.
Let's not see the delusion, okay?
But you just stood up so quickly for yourself, and somebody else was like your fellow Canadian, right?
I know I'm gonna stand up for fucking Kate.
Kate is my girl. I stand up for her.
Now, again, you're standing up for yourself.
You're always quiet until it comes to yourself, isn't it?
Oh, goodness.
Yeah, he doesn't want to have an opinion on anything else.
I mean, is that really that drama?
I mean, he doesn't want to get into the drama, really.
And that's what I say. Like, you can just, you know, that's where the chat goes.
Put me in the chat and give your opinion there.
All you so you just
I like him I like him, but I say this this is where like I'm telling you Christine got mad cuz I didn't
Now I can explain it. This is where Christine got mad and I kind of get it. I said 10%
I don't want him to take side
but if you are gonna take a link and you know it's heated and shit are gonna be fucking talked about you don't sit there and
Look in the air and don't say shit until it comes down to you your name your honor your tradition
Your fucking culture you should stand up for everybody or anybody that you actually think it's right or wrong
Period.
When his name was getting tainted.
You know what I'm saying?
When he was getting cheated, it was a problem.
You get what I'm saying?
Now that it in his name.
I love like, I love like he kind of dry
cause he does stand up.
Even when Christina on the panel, I'm going to say it.
He is going to stand up.
And that's where he challenges.
No, he's not.
No, you're wrong.
He does, he challenges you.
At least we know he's an athlete in our premium race.
I don't sit here and take care of my husband.
I used to take care of my husband.
Said that I unalike children and I don't care who you are in that chat
Okay. Psyche allowed it. Continue to play it. Somebody should have spoke up because you know something?
If anybody knows in ER trometers, they take their weekends, they take their nights, they take their holidays away from their own family.
They worked 12, 16-hour shifts to make sure people's lives are saved. And not a single, well, I shouldn't say a single, there were quite a few.
thought it was funny, but he encouraged her and added more. Yes, I'm pissed because you know
something, I gave up 25 years of me and my family.
to care for other people, for people who were having heart attacks, having
strokes, gunshot wounds, stab wounds on a daily basis. Sorry, didn't mean to get on
my soapbox, but when you cross that line where I take what I do very seriously
because I make one mistake, you or your family dies. Sorry.
I need to take the link and address it get get in front of it stop how like a little bitch. Yeah, it'd be safe
How do I know she meant that is a joke? You know, she made a comment that that my dog Fawzi was abused
Okay, that don't bother me
Because I know better but
I take very serious my profession. I paid a good thing. She's on a bed in a veterinarian then right guys
Good thing. She's not a veterinarian because she doesn't mean fozy you can say what I mean
Chris look at say that and Chris and Christine laugh, but you know and
God forbid and plus with her name. I mean this point is kind of Christian. I don't know
Your name your full name wasn't said I mean
a lot of money for that license.
I have spent a lot of time to educate myself,
get the credentials, go through the extra classes
to become a trauma nurse.
So no, I have no tolerance for even a joke like that.
And neither should any of you.
Because can you imagine you go to an ER? You're having a heart attack. Do you want the first thing in your mind?
Oh God, I remember when Crystal said that that blah blah blah. Can you imagine you had a
Child that got ran over by a car. They call 911 and have to take that child in and you're you're thinking
Oh my god, is this nurse going to unalive my child?
Yeah, I'm sure that's what people are gonna be thinking. Oh my god
Dear god. Well, first of all, no one
Would know who it is besides us and then everyone who does know who it is knows crystal, right?
I mean this come on Christine think about real life here. Okay. I take that serious all this other bullshit
I don't take serious that I do
But some of this stuff is like borderline like
like it's disgusting like you don't want your name by the way how about um christine how about
stan man putting um a crack pipe in your mouth and having the your whole picture on his show and
even though you said he didn't yeah someone put that up there right
I mean, that's a little bit more,
and Sandman led it up there, right?
And this show, he could have taken it down.
That's your freaking picture.
What if I go to the hospital,
I'm like, I don't want my nurse to smoke crack,
and I saw a picture, you know?
That's the same argument you're making basically.
Okay, let's, we'll continue.
I'm attached to some things that is just like,
Professional world that we have there are too many short it gets especially in your trauma
These people are assholes. They fucking are always gonna be a person. They're assholes. They're fucking assholes
When they go to an ER and they need
The ER with me
You have pussies friends. You have pussies friends, sir. You were my friend at one point. You were my friend
Do you think Janet was really your friend versus me?
Well, no, no. At that time, at that time, she was really mad at me
At that time, it was a stepping stone for, I was just stepping stone
At one point, she started the service of being your admin
I can't play in the video, because, well, you know, Chris Kay was in the video too
Like, I play some of these videos multiple times, I mean it's like
Plus I can give calm it when you're playing it you can give comment area like of course crystals crazy and stuff
I mean, it's like it's not like
Anyone took it seriously anybody did one person take it seriously besides even crystal didn't she said
that I'm some old bucket. I don't need that.
That's somebody else's opinion, that's not my opinion.
Well, I did mention that she was watching
Alexandra's movies and stuff,
like that's what she was referring to.
I don't think anyone says you hate black people,
but well, I don't know.
So you're trying to shut that you frame and then on top of it you get mad if anybody else that I fucking fuck with get you like
Bronzeberg did a live about you
Look at him coming over to the stream to cry like a bitch. What are you? Why are you here? Are you here? Why are you here?
Why are you here? So you can complain again?
It's all while beauty this Saturday dirt nobody wants to hear you
Shut the fuck up those I'm sucking his day make you stop up here pussy
No, if y'all is pussies.
Yeah, you fuck.
Be this show, bro, we're not your show.
Can you just give me a chance to see?
You're out chasing, bitch.
Who the fuck you talking to?
This is be this show.
I don't give a fuck, bitch.
I'm talking to you.
But that night, BlackRG was up there with J-Dog, with Janet,
with Groovy Jimmy.
Um, I don't remember you you weren't there and they were saying the most disgusting things about animals and it was it was and they were laughing at all
You banned everybody
And if you don't want to
You know have your nursing thing. How about don't be in the trollverse like how about I don't want my I don't want to troll
As a nurse what about people who think that that's gonna be more of a realistic issue then I don't want you know
Whatever nonsense Crystal was saying what about you know, you're sitting on panels and on public
Internet on YouTube
How about not be a public figure then
No, he did it. He was even there that night banning everybody. He was he was in his feelings as usual and then gets up
He cried
If he and did it, I don't know because a I am subbed B. I don't work C
I don't type. How does she know I was playing it? I mean, it's like. Oh, yeah, because people were sending screenshots. Okay
screenshots
Consider the source of Christine because no, I do not know I do not
Reference my show that you weren't there, but you were typing in the chat
But you referenced that that happened on a show so you were well
No, I was not psyched everybody
You didn't know because I got screenshots and messages
You claimed it was me and I have not been in your chat and do not call me a liar
You are when you say I'm in there
You just you are when you say I'm working. You just had a cry man. You just had a fucking cry about bulls**t.
I cried when my father passed away the last time I cried. Just like you cried when I tried to change things about you.
That's why you cried.
By the way, this panel right here, this was the one where it was supposed to be, everyone was supposed to just let Bita and I talk, right?
And then, if it, and Christine said or stuff, if anyone talks, then they get muted or booted, right?
Okay.
This is that panel other cast way
I was crying and when people are fucking talking about my fucking family members. It's disgusting. It's nasty
Oh my god, I fucking my last name my name
Associated to that. We need Jay dog up out of here site. You need to disown the Nick
I mean, if he can do it, he'll find out, he'll find out about G-Dog himself.
And people, people are saying that Alex is banding, and I'm going to tell you one of
your mods, who you trust, let me know that.
Wow.
And so it's like, you know, she knows a lot about my show for not being there, you know,
it's like, she's talked, oh, one of my mods, okay, so I know, so shame me.
probably. Yeah, but whatever.
I've talked to Alex and he, I told him not to, and he,
Oh my God. He's playing stupid.
Do you not know Alex? We all know Alex.
He's playing stupid for Alex.
Alex was there for me the other night.
I have known Alex for over two years.
I know him. He was there for you the other night,
but has he always been there for you consistently?
It's funny because then you say he sent pieces to your house
and you still sitting there defending him.
I don't get it.
You know how many times that guy threaten your channel
Who talks beta and
Who's ready my pants who's ready who punk porn bomber
That's in her chat that day
Several more streams on you
I'm not defending you because Allied, Allied is definitely no fucking angel, okay?
I'm not fighting people over in my house all day knocking for extra scrap metal, so of course I'm in the house.
I don't, I'm not blaming anybody but when you don't know what to do.
I'm a fucking woman.
I know who it is, Christine.
I have his name because he's shook my knee a little bit.
I don't know anything of him anymore.
Let's talk about that, psyche.
It could be Alexander NYPD.
People can fuck with you all the time at this point.
You look just like you wanted a dog's black RG.
Isn't that right, psyche?
Oh, he going low now.
Fake fuck.
What is he talking about?
He's looking for your information, bronze.
He's looking for my information.
A dog's information.
I want to know his story about him.
I wish you would.
I did say, yeah, because.
I didn't like basically it's like wow bronze bird is having full panels on me
I mean, I don't know I don't know shit about him
So I was like does anybody have a story about him or something something something, you know
I wasn't saying I want his full information to share with the you know, I don't talk to people, okay?
I was saying does he have a story because I don't I want you know
He's gonna do he said he's gonna do every show about me just son, right?
Well, can I do like you know ten minutes on him?
40-50 a mine in his shot so would psyche. I'll get your whole shit the leader. I dare you to dox me
Man no
Months ago. So I went ahead and talks my address my name everything. That's how everyone knows my name or address
Okay, guys, let me just clarify this too. I'm sorry. I don't mean it like I haven't commented thing on this, okay?
So this Katie and her name is you know, she has a name up there
That's all I knew about her I never said her last name and I I just knew her personally through Jamie, right and
so
Then she would come on my panel
under some other, like, very long, laborious name,
uncomfortably numb, right?
And so sometimes I accidentally would say Katie,
and I think I did it maybe a couple of times.
I didn't tell you last name or anything, okay?
I don't know your name or add
When did I do that show me a screenshot show me a audio clip
Why do you think psyche does that maybe is people that he affiliate like discussing people like it's really you're like
I'm just I just want to know what's going on and I'm sorry wrong word
I didn't mean to yell at you because we can't just keep like circling around things
I like Katie say something I wanted either cleared or unclear it or you know as people telling me you trying to dock me
Well, because they're just probably lying to get you riled up or something like that.
I don't dox anybody.
I don't even dox AMC.
What do you mean?
Yeah, you was trying to dox AMC.
I don't know.
I'm not trying to dox anybody.
No, I'm not trying to dox anybody.
I watch the stream, bro.
I'm not stupid.
Oh, Katie Lyon, Sykes.
Oh, Katie Lyon.
Katie is misunderstanding something.
Yeah, I let the kitty in.
I'm misunderstanding.
I'm misunderstanding your fucking mouth.
When did I dox you?
When did I dox you, Katie?
Oh, about a month after I joined the panel.
Okay, I wish you didn't get Jamie in here to discuss this
because Jamie will understand better.
But yeah, I didn't ever dox you.
I don't dox people.
I never give anybody's real names or address
or phone number or anything on my show ever
or anybody else's show.
So I don't know what you're talking about.
So we all lying that when it came to Katie and me,
you trying to get us dox?
I'm lying about you trying to dox.
You trying to get either of you dox.
You guys are, can you guys let me speak?
Maybe, maybe, somebody docks Katie in your chat and you're not aware of it, is that what
happened Katie?
No, it came out of his mouth.
Did I say Katie?
What information did I give about you?
Katie, what information did I give about you?
You don't have to say the information, just what kind of information?
You guys have my address, my entire name.
I think about your whole ad on my show.
You guys have my phone number, everything size.
I did it because I never done that to anybody ever, okay?
Never, I've never given out anybody's full name.
Of course, I have to.
When was this?
You need to leave Jamie out of it.
I don't really, I don't, I don't, I've been working before.
I've been working for over a year.
It doesn't matter.
Maybe Jamie, maybe Jamie and I have a good relationship.
So leave her out of it.
You can stay with her.
Babe Jamie, out of it, I talk to her every fucking day.
so do I so do I so we were out of it yeah we're both friends whatever no psyche is a bad person man
he's a bad omen he doesn't stand for anything he thinks this is like an issue between Katie and Jamie
you know um there there is i have seen like you know foreign but i don't want to get us like
That's it. I don't
Everybody stop it Katie. How would psyche have your doc?
Well, it's already putting in certain I don't want to bring her back into it
Exactly. So that's what he that's why he's never given me information Katie. She's never given me information. Okay?
Why because what happened between us behind the scene you brought it and you use it as content what I did what I
Told you I was like, I
Psyche listen my life is gonna end there's 140 people here. I'm privating it
It's gonna be till tomorrow. I don't go and like make slander put your name last name link you with some disgusting ass shit
I don't co-sign with shit like that, okay?
And he allows baseball, he allows baseball.
I talk to you about it, and what did you do?
You went and handed it over just to make it worse for me.
You know, you hurt, like you hurt me so fucking bad,
you have no fucking clue.
You have no fucking clue.
Like seeing pictures of, you know, your cats,
and they said, you know, I love them.
You played with my fucking emotions,
but you never gave two fucks about what you said
about my family.
He didn't hurt you, he was hateful.
What are they talking about? They're talking about another person, right?
Again, why am I being blamed for what another person is saying, right?
I don't understand. They're talking about somebody else, but I'm being hateful. I mean, it's just ridiculous.
It's so anything.
Off the stream. Go.
Run, baby. Run.
Don't come back, bitch.
That's what you guys like you guys didn't even let me speak to him and it's like I have a headache
No, I'm just I'm gonna keep it real Vita because psyche knows what he's doing when he comes over here
He doesn't want to rekindle no fucking friendship with you
I've seen this over and over and over and over again
But that's the thing. This is my opportunity and like you guys all have had your channel like I'm trying to talk about things
That has never been out there
Okay, I can't talk you guys go ahead and talk go ahead. No go ahead and I'll shut up
Backstage um next time backstage um everybody includes it just seems like as soon as I say a fucking sentence
I can't finish it. That's all I'm trying to say
I'm trying to fucking actually say something to him with facts and proof like he said that I read his fucking messages
What did he do before I read his fucking messages? He said like what I told them I said like this is like discussing
Allegations being made on me. I'm gonna take legal action. He went and handed it to the person that I said
I'm gonna take legal action on she made a whole fucking video about me saying like
I'm racist against blacks, I'm into fucking porn, blah, blah, blah.
The thing that I want to talk about Psych2 is his affiliations, not anything else.
Because I've been around the blocks and I know these people.
I don't think he really knows.
But keep interrupting and we'll never get him on the panel to have a decent interview.
Never.
Let him talk.
Those needs to go backstage though.
Sorry, not sorry.
The what's up here? So like he doesn't feel like every he's being attacked by everybody
Let's even say anything
Did he even say like a word? I mean, I haven't heard him say a word. It's just the only reason she said that is because
He like, you know, we're friends. I don't know
Post is not offering nothing. He's just dick-sucking psyche. I don't want to hear that bullshit right now. Yeah
It's just been there's stuff going on like plus pizzas and plus the you know
The manure sent to my house and stuff like that. So a lot of stuff is happening to me, too
And so I understand how bad it feels. Yeah, I
So when it happened to me, um, did you know where the actually root causes were?
Did you know a J-dog had a big, big, big part of all this?
Yeah, that's allies. That's allies get down.
Is allied my mod?
Uh, no, he's not my mod either. He's, uh, but he is on the panel.
J-dog is your mod, isn't he?
We're up there with him.
You're managing, right?
You unmodded me?
Jamie, Jamie's my only managing mod.
That was Christine. She admitted to it.
Christine, you're trying to outside.
No, I most certainly did not find out anybody today.
I'm talking stop picking up.
I know you have a little crush on Christine.
Just stop it Joe.
I'm Christine again, if I didn't apologize to Christine, it is like your power. He's not accepted. I'm sorry
Hey, that's fine. That's fine. That's at least I try to do it again
So if you say he never apologized, you know, you have it right here. I did try to apologize
But you showed it over and over and over
Messages you were accusing me of everybody you don't know coming in as me and you just told me I do work and I
Haven't I'm sorry if I if I misunderstood or if I misconceived that I apologize. No, you lied
I didn't lie. It was misunderstanding. It wasn't me like I'm saying like saying something that I knew was not true
I thought it was so
That's it. It's like not I agree with you black archie. So fucking much
So much all of this bullshit even like you're you what you did a black card G
Um, all cut it was resolved everything was always resolved until fucking J-Dog and other people decided they want a little bite of this fucking
Attention, right? You have these newbies up here and acting like they're your best friend and they know you so fucking well
Enemy now, and it's like that we're friends and so it's like it maybe and we're not this is not a war
You said it was a war and also I remember Sam and saying
This is war
Come on everyone against like
Myself there's a war you guys are men you guys can play this war for me and Christina's reality
It really hurt us because we cared about you. I hate that fake motherfucker
I don't want to be I don't like this fake motherfucker. I don't like me over me again. Yeah, I am what you're gonna do about it
I'm gonna leave and so then you then get the fuck out
The same thing happens like he when I try to join your panel with other people they attack me, you know
It's gone really far. Like I'll do a live and this is just gonna be I will like, you know
You might get clipped or am I not I'm gonna private it
But then we got people that are gonna be leeches and little fucking scumbags like Alexander fucking
Mayors calling my putting my name my name
I'm gonna say it right now. My name, very unique, Bita. My last name, very unique. You know what
it is. In her titles and linking my whole fucking family to disgusting shit. How about you hold
other people accountable before you come here and press like bronze bird about having a live about
you. He didn't even know her that long. I recommend, I told him, I said,
I loved how you guys had like a connection. I mean, in my mind, um, she like, you know,
is doing better because I, I know about her how she does this to other people, but
I know like she went through a loss and she was like, you know, I mean, I'm different and she moved to California
I saw a whole different energy with her, you know for a couple months. I observed it and I was like, you know what?
She's cool. She's like chillin. I actually recommended them together. She knows that she said beta
Thank you for introducing me to psyche and the same thing. So I have no issues with that
But you're gonna sit her and let her fucking say that I'm like off
Eric Carter, my ex-husband.
I'm part of a mastering child trafficking.
I, my ex-husband, my whole family has a porn addiction.
My ex-girl is involved and wants to kill her in Minecraft.
Come on, Psyche. Make an AI song about her lunatic ass before you tell me who you fucking care about.
Vita, Vita. Alex says that about everyone, so I understand she's talking about you sometimes.
I mean, like, why is he, like, sitting here and getting upset that, like, other people are, like...
Upset like look at the shit she's saying about me. She should delete her fucking messages. That's what she should do
Bullshit in her post about me. That's where me and you can come to an understanding
Otherwise, I want nothing to do with you. It's not even about J-Doc because J-Doc is just a little cockroach
He doesn't have a channel. She wants to put my fucking name out there that fucking bitch. You visited her. She visited you
Don't visit me. Don't come here
That's not a really good question, you know why?
Because I will tell you this, I like you, KK.
Hey, Gus.
What's up, dude?
Sorry. Oh, is that clip almost over now? You can keep playing it if you don't want to go on. So yeah, let's have a little break
Yeah, we can have a little break home. I just want to tell you that I timed somebody out in your chat, which I've never done before
Okay, cool, was that cool, I mean you
Second of all dude, I had something to say about what you're watching though. Yeah
Would you have stayed if they were to let me join like in stage?
Would I have said if they would have let or they wouldn't have let you join?
No, if they would have because you know, I guess Christine was calling this
Well, I'm not you know, I'm not gonna talk shit
They kicked me they kicked me but the only reason that be to let me up because she's like cuz
Psyche feels like he's attacked, but how did it feel when it was five versus one rep?
And you were even talking like I didn't hear you say one
Yeah, I mean it's like maybe
Piece of what sometimes I do
I understand. I understand. Well, you know, I think they're gonna go into like how I have a friend
You know, I think his name is tyler, right? Um, and he
You know, she kicked him off for five bucks, you know, and he I wasn't on the panel at the time
He just came up on his own without me
asking for anything and just was
You know, I'm talking about that he's a he's like he's the other gay guy in the panel verse. He's like
Tyler I think right and uh
Yeah, he's like really nice guy, but he was just like oh, he's really friendly and he's really any all he was doing is saying
Hey, well, you know, I'm friends with psych. I like psych a lot
We're you know, we're both, you know, yeah guys or whatever and go through each other
You watch this whole thing they ever let me join
Like I think I think there's another there's a there's another panel. They show where you do maybe I'm not I forgot kind of I've watched a little bit
They kicked you off already this panel
Or I think I think this might have been later in the show
I don't remember. I think I don't know if I came back or someone told me to come back to it
I don't remember. Well, I think I'm not gonna call trouble or nothing, but I do you think that's fair game
I think if you're talking about someone
Especially when he's not there to defend himself, but even if he's there, but it's five versus one
I feel like you can like it's not even phone her friend. Let's say we fucking hated each other. I it's an open panel
I think you know be able to be up there
But then it's an afterwards in their panels be that you know, she's pretty good about it like she'll let me join
But they all these other people, you know, they they call they're like, oh, that's they used to call me Tony
Now the new thing is except Alex, but now the new thing is I'm psyche's boy
Yeah
Because I know it kind of annoys you I mean it's like they just know they know I'm gonna defend you and they're trying to like
Get me going but they kind of realized it's not a really good thing to get me going because then you know
Then we'll actually get into a real thing going you know, and I love that shit
I love the debate a little bit. Just a tiny bit not too much. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah with me for a minute. I mean, let's watch a little bit more. Let's see. Let's watch a little bit
I'm down over hang out for a little bit. Okay. Okay. Here we go
But if you were getting attacked and your name was being drives into shit and this guy
Let's see who's here. Let's see if you someone's in the back. Let's see. This is Apollo. Come on up Apollo
What do you think so far Apollo? He was in the car. He met her Calima era
Calima era
Where does that mean? Good more good morning in Greek. Oh, yeah, and that's I it's Greek
Yeah
I
Call me Merah Merah Cali Merah
Yeah, you ain't fucking Greek. I went to I've been to Greece and I follow his nose Greek
Even your Greek right up. He loves Greece. I know right
You know, like I said, I'm born there. I'm born there
He's Greek
They talk like you
I'm living over 40 years in German. Okay. Yeah, so I guess I've more I've more more the German accent than the Greek accent
Okay, you know you once you said that I kind of like now I can hear it though
Yeah, but I am you know, so but this I mean this is pretty crazy
I think they but they I think this was the panel where they're like, okay one at a time
I'm not 100% sure but they were like, you know someone we're just supposed to be like yeah
And might be talking on it and then it's like everybody else
Yeah, I haven't been keeping up. I do got one like when you watch club, I get obviously to channel, but uh
like you got it like uh
and then like explain like
especially when you were talking
I know, I know you were
but like explain your point of stuff
but you didn't really
well you did have a point
but let me not misspeak
and like contradict myself here
but like earlier when you were talking
and like
I think that's why they didn't let me join
because they all knew
I was gonna be like
no you're not gonna over talk
you'd like let the man talk
and then they knew I was gonna have your back
so fuck
Yeah
That was like the reason like you eventually you did get kicked off of it, but it's like you weren't even like
Like you really bought it. We weren't doing anything wrong
You just said you hold Bronzeberg to quiet down because he was kept interrupting me and be there
Right now. I think he should well now never mind. I won't say that
Don't hate on bronze but don't hate on bonds with he's only a puppet
Yeah, I agree. I see I haven't said have I said anything about him like he's saying all this shit about me on the panel
I've just I'm sitting here like you know not
I'm very calm and I'm not trying to attack anyone personally
I'm trying to give the facts and stuff and so
Let me put it back. Is it up? Okay, so let's watch
Yeah, I don't really talk too much shit
I just do it to like because I know I can get still certain like
debate
Yeah
Like a year ago, I used to love to do it with Alex, but it's not fun anymore. You see it's like there's five
This is all like this is all like a little club right here, right? This is all like
No, there's a little so it's nice. Listen
Good thing. This is this is a lot. I had panels with these people
11 against me 11
I know this is kindergarten. This is kindergarten bullying. Oh, that's a light work. I had I had 11 of these of these fools of these
Muppets one girl Christine against me 11 and I didn't have a curse one time. I
Let them curse and you know, I'll say Christine does like, you know, she likes she does like to silence
People, you know, but she's a control freak. She's a control freak. Trust me. I know her
That's what she hates me
She's a control freak
Yeah, you don't know about what? Um ghost I
Don't know. Sorry to say that. I don't know enough about everyone. Yeah
Like we played another video earlier tonight where Christine said
Okay, now, Eldo, I have to go, but Eldo, you have to stay up here, because Bita is so nice that she needs, you know, you to intervene if Psyche comes up.
So that's what she said.
Like she should try.
You know, like Bita should try and then take a conversation, two adults have a conversation, you and her.
No.
Fuck that.
He was gonna try to debate her.
I mean, I've tried to get Psycho to debate.
He won't do it.
He's too nice of a guy to do it.
So I was trying to just to talk to beat it like that's all I wanted to do
On her panel, but and then it's like you know the other show
It was like I finally like tried to make the like, you know ten minutes and she wouldn't do the ten minutes
Okay, so one-on-one. That's what I meant
So honestly if you I'll be honest with you right now
So like this is just I'll be completely honest with you
If you had like six people up here and beta join and they were all beating up on her
You know what I would do
I would literally take her position and defend her
Well, I mean, it's like I just kicked everyone off and just had it went on one with those
Because that's what I've been trying to do and so we did get her a little bit
She just wanted to talk about
Here being on the RV or something like that make some kind of dumb dumb little point that didn't even matter
That's what she wanted to talk about. So
But anyway, so you've got you've got to stop though once if it does end you got to stop
Yeah, everybody
Let's watch some more
I think fucking name like if all this disgusting shit
He wouldn't be concerned about what he was doing. You would be protecting your fucking family last name too. That's what I care about
What happened hold on what happened
That happened home. That's not the end. It was about the time she was really mad at that time. It was a stepping stone
I was just a stepping stone. You know you are
At one point, she served the service of being your admin. I thought she wasn't
Was that is this was it I played the whole thing already about the end. I
Played the whole thing already. Oh, that's come confused. Hold on
really, I
Thought there was more to this whole she does this to other thing. Okay. I guess that was the end. I mean
You know, that's pretty
But did I miss something did I skip something? I'm not sure you might just get I don't know whether I wasn't watching
I don't I thought was there more let me just check one more time because it seemed like there was more to it than that
Nothing was like an hour or two
Okay
Okay, yeah, I played the whole thing. Well, okay. Well, that was it, you know
It's like that was that part of it, you know, and then we we did watch the other one the other one was really good
I did everyone. I love everyone saw some of it
But hey, what's up Joe? I do want to show you a little bit the other one because the other one
I'm not gonna play the whole thing because it was like it's kind of like long
But I do want to show you just a couple parts of it
It was and not just to like try to edit or whatever, but I I'll cut out my my most of my what I was saying, but
Want to show you the panels on that because the panels were pretty interesting. They were just brutal brutal on me
So let's see. Let's see. It's this one right here
You can watch a little bit of this one. So this is pretty good
Here we go. Thank you for guys for sticking in. Hey, what's up guys much a little bit more of this here we go
The scrapper army episode
Having a live about me. I'm getting stuff sent to my house
People looking for scrap metal and stuff, right? I'm just here to cut a promo
You know, I fit Kate. I feel like we're going to war the scrapper army is gonna descend onto
He's house once again. It could be it. It could be tomorrow. It could be next week
He'll never know but guess what psyche those scrappers are coming for you and I hope you've got the metal
Yeah, psyche. Well, I don't know that he's tweaking out
But the him and beta stuff I think is really getting to him. My thing is I've witnessed the multiple
Attempts of him trying to work it out and just talk one-on-one with beta and it's like someone always
Someone's talking. I want him to fight back and I feel like he doesn't get that chance because it's always a dog pile on him
Um, Aldo, please stay up here or come back up.
If Sack happens to come up, let me let them, and then if you need to intervene, because
Bita needs that support, because she's too nice.
Sorry, Bita, you're too new.
You're just done with the drama?
Well, you're in the middle of it now, because you come in and say, oh, you're too new, you
old friend.
I'm so sick of people saying that.
You're obviously not my friend.
You focus on you and I never did anything wrong. I never did. What did I do wrong to you for you to like just like
It's like every day can you pause it? Can you pause it please?
Yeah, little trick see that's that's what's for me. That's what's a medical moment at the calm moment
She acts like she is the mother of Obeda, although Obeda is a little child. She's a grown woman.
She's not 12, she's a grown woman.
She's 50 years old. I mean, I'm not to give to her.
Oh, okay. I don't know that. Okay. Whatever.
No, no, it's not her fault. She's more than her fault.
No, it's not her fault. She's capable to speak for herself. Who is Christine?
to act like she is the protector of the gate, she is not a military man, she is a creator of the spectrum
and then put a guard dog, put Eldor as a guard dog, as a bully
to not let you talk with her. Who is she to give this kind of commands?
Right, I know it's that way. I heard that and I'm so glad like trip kick always gets these moments like that are yes
exactly
people need to hear this
People need to hear this moment when she says about elbow. Don't let them talk. Yes
This is a medical moment
Yeah, this is anything about the character of Christine
She because if you and her beta fix your problems, okay
Then she lose control of a beta and she never gonna let it happen
Yeah, and and then beat it was like well, I think she'll go play again, but we just like oh
I love you Chris. It's just like, you know, it's like excuse me. She's like cuz you're so you're too nice beta
Wow
You can't be nice break, but she's not she's too nice, especially like when she's talking to me
She's not I mean she's been okay. She was okay in those like the last one, but she gets I mean, yeah
It's like let me ask you a real question for real though. Does be on a panel where there's five versus one
Against me yeah
She was on the Bronzeberg one. She was twice. She was on both of those episodes of the Bronzeberg ones
I remember I joined the panel 12 not this panel, but I joined a panel where she was on there
And it was twice and I actually had her believe that I had her back
Uh-huh. Well, I think I've seen I saw you know, I saw me to defend me a couple times against it like we're you know
We're against Katie and stuff like Katie was like you dropped me and it's like I should be just like I don't know about that
This shit
Katie yes, she's sort of talking shit. She's like you talk to me motherfucker, and I was like
I like to address I like to address the Hanna on something Hanna I'll small and then he's on a vertical, okay
No, you have what you wish for
He's the war in German. Okay
That's not allowed, I'm gonna sleep.
Okay, it was a joke, it was a joke.
Yes, okay.
But yeah, and so here's me just upset a little bit.
This guy and his granddaughter are looking for scrap money.
It didn't happen again, it didn't happen again, it didn't happen again.
They have that guy on the show, it's a patriotic show,
and I apologize if I would react this way.
Shut up.
But it's like...
You know, my feelings are hurt too and everyone's acting like I'm just this hurtful mean person and I'm not it's like I get pushed into a corner and
I
Get upset. I think it's getting to him. I almost feel bad. Oh
I agree, Kate. It's definitely getting to him
Alex you can't when we played the clip not so why are you doing this site?
The reason I like you both because you were different than them you
Okay, Alex, come back. Okay, Alex. It's not appropriate
I just said let's watch this clip because it's interesting because Kate is not like my biggest fan
We know this right, but she's not my biggest fan, but look she's
Sticking up for me like and that's saying something like if Kate is sticking up for me
I know that you know, there's something right there's something that's me like he is going
Sure, I'll have you back up just like Alex. You just watch from the backstage right now because it's like we're having a little calm
But I just went yeah, just watch this clip real quick
thing is I've witnessed multiple attempts of him trying to work it out and
just talk one-on-one with Bita and it's like someone always intervenes someone
yes I'm like why does it have to be like that and always to her benefit it's
always someone coming to her her defense and I kind of
sort of feel bad a little bit for him because
Right his mic's always so quiet and everyone screams over him. It's annoying. Yeah, or like
He said he got kicked off Samans panel like
So that
Or fishy fingers, I don't I wish I could um
I want to, I want to like take over and scream for him and like fight for it because like, I just like, oh my God, but this has been going, they feel like this every week. I know it's just, I don't feel bad like that beat us, but I like, I just want him to have a fighting.
And so I just sit there like, oh, no, get louder, get assertive.
I want him to fight back and I feel like he doesn't get that chance because it's always a dog pile on him.
I just want to see him like be able to stand on his own and battle beta one on one.
Then it seems like she always has some army behind her and it's.
Psyche is literally the male version of Beacon Patriot.
Yeah, it's a lot.
It's a lot of fucking bullshit, I love it.
I just saw somebody send me like a screenshot.
Fucking, that's the shit that I gotta deal with.
I give like people chances and I gotta deal with that,
you know?
Are you serious, Barry?
You're my fucking mod and you're like looking
to fucking give all my information to people.
And then you're telling me you're the person.
W
Somebody else is like oh my god like beta look look at very very he's like saying all this fucking shit about you
And like egging on freaking like Shannon some lady named Shannon up there like always like fucking ranting
I'm like, okay. Yeah, I don't even really like
Which one was the real sound man
like he when he allows people like Vita's uncle as you know
I don't think Katie's, I'm sorry, they're talking about like Shannon, Shannon and Samion and stuff and I don't know if it's too real.
I honestly think he is, unless somebody wants to admit to it truthfully and prove it to me, I think he is Psyche HIV and that one did get banned and that's the one he was typing under.
HIV, um, awakens tarot alt. Okay. That's Christine accusing me of being
I agree and even be it in beta. Yeah, she does offend me here because
that's Christine. That is just like the stupidest thing I ever heard. Right. I'm going to put
HIV psyche awakens tarot and plus you saw the person in my chat for several times today
If you were here earlier in the chat the person came in the chat several times today
They are banned in my chat. I would not have an alt name that okay. I do have
Several accounts right I have several accounts, but I'll tell you what they are
They're Elon Musk, Nicolas Cage, and then the rest are like psyche awakens or you know, there's not any
No, nothing like it. They don't troll on them. I haven't used them. I've never used them. I haven't used them for months
I use them on Emma's maybe a little bit, you know, and I never use them on any show or anything like that. Basically, I
Just have a lot of email addresses and so I have I do have a few accounts and I so I've talked about I've had alts on
Emma's and stuff not
Not anything and I've never used it in this panel verse. I swear to God. Okay, swear to God
Maybe he didn't realize what he's blaming elder. He's saying that's elder is all he was like elder
Oh, that's elder elder is saying this
Yeah, yeah, dude you're Tony
I know it's me it's just me
By the way, two fresh bags of manure at my door today, then there's a man looking for a lawnmower
And there's a man a man really got really mad when I said there was no scrap metal here
He was like motherfucker like that happened to me today. So that was
Menards you can buy it for like a couple dollars. It's yeah, so it's literally a dollar bag. Okay, by the way
Brings like green and blue so it makes like a friendly family time if you're not crooked
You burn it. Yeah, I mean, maybe I'll just burn some in the fireplace. I have a garden and stuff, but yeah
But what
Have you ever burnt copper?
I've burnt copper. I'm okay. I think yeah, it burns a beautiful green color. That's the same thing right green blue
green and blue
Yeah, but but I know I'm not like and then Eldo's gonna say like oh, well I burn myself
Okay, if you guys know like I'll hold on like I'll show you this this is like as I sell this burn on my arm
I woke up one day and I had
Strange burn on my arm and it was like these it's like a three thing and as he although is convinced that I did it to myself
For attention or something. It's still there. Okay. Do you know?
Yeah, you want to why?
I'll be honest with you Paula
And I hate to say it because this is my brother right here, but it's because you're fucking with those cards at 3 a.m
You never fuck with him. Oh
It was like it happened look up at like 7 a.m
But I had like fell asleep at like 5 and I wasn't drunk when I fell asleep. So that's what I know that I know that I didn't
Accidentally do it and forget about it. Do you happen to put one happen to my sleep? Okay. Why do you happen? It's weird
I also was gonna say I did it to myself to get attention. Okay. That is another stupid thing. I don't self-injure. Okay
Wouldn't I have like marks all over my body or something? Why would I just one day decide to do that?
It's just like the stupidest thing I've ever heard, right? It was weird
I do think it was a supernatural thing, but I don't think it was because of tarot cards, but
I'm not saying that you're saying
Hey, I'm just saying like if you don't want to be like let's just say you don't want to get in fight with the toughest guy at school
You probably shouldn't talk to him. You know what I'm saying? You probably shouldn't invite that shit in just saying
What are you talking about? You're talking about like I don't know
Does the first time it's happened and it's like come on it's not easy with cards it has to do maybe with
demonic attack maybe but not to do with me
Doing cards. It's just it's like you can say, you know math flash cards could do the same thing
I mean, it's like
There's always is a tool for interpretation. Okay, but let's continue this one second
Why are you banning people and protecting psyche when he allows people like Vita's uncle as you know, all names like
Towards like protecting him. You know, I'll be like, okay fine. I'm gonna delete that. That's a disgusting name
But then he has like people called betas uncle
Does anybody ever seen betas uncle in the chat and if they did I mean I have a lot of people in the chat
They're are named betas something or other in the in the in the ban list
I've seen but I've never really seen an active participant on the panel with that name. Okay if I saw that name
I would delete I would kick that person off right away. Okay
There is a person named Bita needs AA, but that person, it was like, it was like, I didn't
take it as seriously, you know.
I would have like another name like Bea's uncle.
I would definitely say, hi, Bea's uncle.
And I would not mod Bea's,
but there was somebody that I maybe didn't hide
that had that name, but I haven't seen him for a while.
I'm pulling around in this fucking chat
and he doesn't even give a shit.
Well, I'm telling you, I think that
HW1 is him. I truly do. Especially after yesterday when he said that he is blocked and after he jumped down, like within less than 30 seconds, he typed something with his name.
No.
You're saying I don't believe that because I don't think he would we use an alt like that to discuss to his own name
He's very careful. Oh my god
You know, I don't like remember when a blogger had blogger awakens tarot and I banned him
I mean, I think there's an everyone at the lake awakens tarot. So that was a whole thing
I'm discussing remember that when everyone started like
kisha wakens tarot and stuff and i started banning everyone with that name and then it was like some
people just didn't mean it like a new way it's like hiv wakens tarot christine you know maybe i
don't think you're an unintelligent person christine but i think this is a reach okay okay this is a
this is like ridiculous basically ridiculous but it's already been target
It's very childish. Yeah, well, it's just really offensive to you. I'm not gonna go around
Slandering my own name like okay. It doesn't make sense. I have a discussion, okay?
At this point, I would not put anything
past him and there is
Katie me that's not real. Yeah, I just found them right now. Got it. Thank you. Yes. Thank you
But he does use alts
Oh, I mean he said he's used alts, but I mean, I don't know if he's gonna go as far as you know, you think like
What better way what better way back stage we put once I can listen
Anything
Capable of doing this. I mean look at me. I'm capable of anything and look at he's putting someone's picture up
this is what we do. I was looking at the comments of uh uh if Hannah wants to join uh I think
Hannah you want to join I'll put the link down I mean come up now come up and uh and I give it to
you person to person in your element Alex is sitting backstage and uh hold on a second I said Hannah
Okay, here we go. Yeah, Hannah come on up. I'll put the link down for you
Okay, here we go. That'll be cool. Okay, here we go. There we go
Okay, there you go. Here we go. Okay
To his arm saying he was asleep when I happened to him then he's capable of making that all
Okay, and that's not me. Okay. I didn't create all he mad because I said leave that all in the chat
It's no it's not wrong with that. Oh, you know, that's the only thing I said, but me being that all no
That's not me. I have to them for your site then leave
It's not that hard leave
It's okay site because remember people's names are in there people's dogs animals are there
Be careful
Live, I saw it in KK's chat, somebody sent me a screenshot where Barry's like,
Vita, bitch, I could have offered, I could have paid, got paid for a hundred.
It's like, why would you even say that?
Like, if you want to go ahead and get the money, why, you know, why are you saying that?
Like, I thought you were like, cool with me, Barry.
I don't get that shit at all.
This nigga Barry was glazing, saying and talking about Cook VB, Cook VB.
I need you to come up here to Cook VB.
I mean, no disrespect to Shannon, but then she couldn't even hear her.
She lost her voice.
Like, you know what I'm saying?
What the fuck?
Come on, man.
Shannon said she was going to retire, Shannon, stick to being retired, you know?
Stay off the internet, Shannon.
Yeah, I'm saying no disrespect man or disrespectfully. I don't really care, but you know, I'm saying like
She said I apologize to her what the fuck did I apologize to her for I've never had to apologize to her
I've never done shit to her look
I don't really like fuck with her because I know she's going through her medical stuff and all that stuff
Shannon, I was like, I don't you know, I wish her that like she has a good recovery and all that stuff
But what the fuck do I need to apologize to her for she made up a bunch of stories about me because she thinks like raging demon is some
Great white and night like, you know, I don't know if somebody with credibility and so honest
And she was like saying that he said like pictures of me like videos on me full naked. I don't have that like are you kidding me from raging demon?
She's like, I won't show like that like I don't I have it with you first of all
You're saying you have videos of me in your phone
But you're gonna bring it up like and line she lies a lot she she lies a lot that woman Shannon
Lies a lot. Yes, I have to step down. I have to handle a few things but
although
Will you stay up here or come back up if Sike happens to come up at me, let them and then if you need to intervene, because Bita needs that support because she's too nice, sorry Bita, you're too nice.
Holy shit.
I love you Christine, you're so sweet.
People need to understand what she's saying.
I tried, I did try.
Time said she'd go one-on-one. I don't know, maybe you must have understood, but no, she wasn't planning on doing that. She was gonna have all five people up there.
Sam and Eldo, I mean, what the fuck? Isn't she ridiculous? Oh, no conditions
All I said is that can we go one-on-one and then not since someone you know
Someone sends money to clap me in the middle of my sentence not to clap me which happened on salmon the last three times
It happens on summer's channel. So and then she is clapping. She clapped my friend for five dollars, right?
Talk about you know. Oh my god. I'm my desperation. Just one person offended me one time. She kicks him off
For five dollars, right? I never slept anyone for five dollars except it was like, you know five dollars a minute or five dollars for five minutes
Yeah, it's ridiculous
It's ridiculous. It's stupid. It's like I tried guys. I tried I did try
I thought I was live. I was live.
I have a question for you, Psyche.
Yes.
I tried to explain myself, okay?
In the beginning, I joined your panel.
I picked no one's side.
I'm not for your side.
I'm not here to defend you, okay?
Don't misunderstand me.
I'm not here to defend you or to attack you.
But let's be fair.
Let's be fair.
If someone comes on your panel,
They make the same demands that you made to be there. Would you allow it?
No, I mean on my panel I would be on my panel and I kicked everybody off
It was one-on-one and nobody was making accusations about her or anything. I mean, it's like, you know, like
Really one dollar to get a sentence raised paid ten dollars to get someone cake paid like it's not demands like
Right, I know I
And it was like in the guy that got kicked for five dollars
I wasn't even there on the panel on Vita's panel that day
It was him him came up on his own and he was just talking one-on-one Vita at that point
And so I've met I mean it was like I would say a hundred dollars
I can kick someone and I pay a hundred dollars you better kick someone
Right, okay, but yeah, that was the you know, you had prepaid for some
But I mean, it's like in Sam and does that too. He's like, you know, but I mean
You can believe it's not fair, but we all do the same shit like yeah
To kick me 25 dollars
Yeah, you pay me I'll pay you $5. I'm gonna get some sucky sucky
Yeah, $5 was like that was that's really cheap for like just I mean because of course like you know
I was like it's like but she then she's mad at me for like, you know, she was always talking about how
Horrible I was to have a clapping system and now she's you know, but she was happy to do it for like, you know
Five times cheaper than I than I did
Like you you are my I don't want to call you is what you're not but I believe you're a man
and I believe she's a woman I don't want to I don't want anyone I'm trying to have
I'm not trying to show proof we need proof of this the burden of proof is on you prove it
burden on me I think that the dude has a dick in the female house of prove your man prove your man
I can show you a goal. Yeah, I can just show goals, but then I got in trouble, so I was in my speedo,
you guys didn't have a little bit of fun.
Why does it feel like you only have like, well, maybe me and I wasn't even, I'm fucking retarded,
but, but Bita was there, she had five, six people. Why do you think that is? Do you think there were
Sims? Do you think that that's why she had an army? That's of course why it was. Yeah, exactly.
And five against one and psyche is not even a fucking debater. He doesn't even like to debate the motherfuckin
I was just trying to talk to her, you know, that's all so exactly let's say
Like five big-ass fucking dudes don't want to fight me. It's like I don't want to talk you guys are not trying to fight me
Like what's the point? I'm trying to be your friend, but fuck it
Yeah, that's why I did so bad when you left, but I did talk I didn't talk shit
But I told you I've been trying to tell you you I did like that burden of proof
You brought up those like even uh, who was that Christie whoever was young you and you're like when the fuck did I ever do that?
And you were like alright, where's the proof that I do I fucking love that like that's how you should be like hey
Where's the proof that you're saying I did it like where's the proof when the woods though one time bring it up right now?
We're like when's the one time I've ever done that I did like that though
Shit. Okay, here we go. Fuck. You know, like a lot of people in chat would like to see that
I just don't understand
Shit and chat, but they never joined and I don't want to be mean to them
I'm literally just like to have a conversation like there was one two girls. I actually like Nancy and I don't like her fuck
I don't actually I don't know her but Hannah said like oh you're playing both sides of the fence
I'd like for her to come up here. I don't want to debate. I don't argue. I was just like her
You buy the cool
Six sides of the fence. I joined six different band with brother. I'm playing six sides of the fence did not both sides
So I'd like to I'd like to for her to like how I play besides
Just use there to like back him up. It's me guess he's gonna debate for psyche. It's me
Yeah, do you hear anybody else defend? Yes. He's a grown man. He can defend himself
They're grown ask me and I agree sir. And that's it. I agree
But who else debates for oh who else like defend him besides me in
This in this this big world. It's only me. Why should why should anyone defend him? Why?
Why should I defend him or I defend him?
Thank you. Well, I mean it's like
I think he's uh, you know brother-in-arms, I think he's a he's a friend of mine
Why would I not defend him if it's five against one?
He's getting bullied and I don't necessarily disagree with everything he's saying and like they're bullying him for saying like
What he said wasn't wrong. I'm gonna defend him
Thank you
If I'm there I can defend myself if I'm not there then it's like I'm happy to have someone
You know sit speak up maybe for me if like it's just being slander, but that's anybody
You know, it's like that's what Vita said earlier. She's like well
It's nice to have
He's not here to defend himself, so we shouldn't talk about him. I literally always say that
Okay, so this is almost over. I'm sorry. I know we're going kind of me. Let me just play let me see if
How much is this? Yeah, this goes on for a little bit. Hold on. I just want to yeah
This is basically just me talking to him
But I just want to play the almost the very end here look at this very end if he did a good job with this one
I'll just put the end of it here watch stuff
And they don't pay for the pizza though.
And so it's not pizza, it's just an unpaid pizza
that I'm expected to pay for.
And so I have to send the disappointed Mexican pizza lady
away and stuff.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Okay, so it hurts.
People I love turn on me for her again and again and again.
They got HK Memphis Shea, they got Sweet Pea,
all these people, they're constantly harassing
with the biscuit song.
Look at her thing.
Oh, biscuit queen.
What is it?
Is it about something other than trying to fuck with me?
I don't think so, because that's a 14 year old meme
that she begged me to play on my show.
And I was like, no.
Then I write a biscuit song called Bita's Biscuits.
And it's like, oh, that's harassing.
It's a good, it was a good nature.
I love you, Gaudi.
Oh, Gaudi.
I love you too.
I think you're a good person.
I think that it's like, Bita's turned you against me.
I'm gonna take a taxi to the far side of the street.
And you should know that he was wrong, you got me feelin' muted, I'm about to get booted,
drama's overcomputed.
Can I work it out with anybody?
No.
Give it a rest.
All I want is chaos at its best, do you see the yes?
That was it.
So anyway, here we go.
I
Well you guys go ahead because it has nothing to do with the topic
Right
One question
What are we doing this weekend man? Are we doing something Saturday? Yes, we're gonna have a party
One do you like an open pan or something? Yes
Yeah
Let's do it
Yeah, I'm down
Like I said, man, I've been I haven't been living hard nothing, but I had a way to whole fucking like
Technically two months for my fucking first paycheck, but luckily I had a lot saved up so I'm not hurt at all, but
Love you
What are we doing about and another thing? What are we doing about Alex? Oh Alex now we can have him on tonight, right?
Yeah
I'm sorry. Hey money for 20. How are you? You can come up Alex now. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, they paid the can you control his volume?
Yes, Alex, can you please have your volume on half, please?
The automatically adjust half
Sorry Alex, I'm really annoyed. Okay. I'm just really annoyed because oh something else, but oh God is
I'll get accused of all this kind of stuff, so I'm not going to say anything right now.
I'll talk privately, but I'm just really freaking annoyed about something, but it's okay.
I'll work it out. Everything will work out. Alex, you can come up now and talk. I need
to maybe go backstage for a second, too, because something just happens. So I'll figure it out.
Come on up, Alex. I think I need a drink. I need to get my liquor out.
Alex is not that bad. Alex is not that bad. Alex is not that bad. Alex is not that bad.
Stream yard, okay. You saw it, right? You know about this?
Yeah, okay. Yes. Oh, so I went he like, you know tag me like a hundred times like I know went over to the stream art
It was named after me whatever psyche psyche
Oaken's TV his panel was called that and he had one called the people's podcast and stuff like that because he wanted to like
You know to lure people in there
He I watched them, but I mean didn't really have to because they were completely there's no speaking in it
there's no video and it was just the stream yard blank screen and
I have like people like say open panel. He's like, oh, I didn't want to have an open panel. I just wanted to hide people
He just wanted to hide people so
No, no the right yeah green screen
Oh shit, my bad
Trust me if Alex learned to control himself and not go to this all you bitch you whatever all this
He has some really good points. He's has some really good points. I mean
Going up and down and then I don't know. He loses it. It's very fast
Name-calling and the blah blah blah makes no sense
Yeah, I mean, yeah, Alex and it's like and usually what happened the other day Apollo
Because Alex was like I just wanted to hide people I was like, okay
Well, that's a little bit of like a red flag. That's like that seems like a little bit
Cuckoo to me to like just wanted to do the panel
This guy is my mod. Okay, then there is this person named
Guadalupe guacamole in the chat and he's like, oh this bitch is that stalker?
This is a gross disgusting
You know he's just like saying horrible things about this Guadalupe and I was like what and then he hid this
Okay, well he couldn't go out and I was like I was like Alex your mod I say Alex your mod you cannot call
People in the chat bitch. I mean is it you just can't it's like
So, as a mod, I just can't have that, right?
So, I took his wrench away.
He got hit and he got timed out or something, but then, and then she, but he had already
hit in the squad of loot papers.
And so I had unhidden her.
She came on the panel.
She was like one of the sweetest people I've ever met in my life.
Like she was just like, she had a little cute little avocado avatar with the chick.
Hi, I'm Kwok, and she's like this little cute little voice,
and she's like the nicest lady, and then she's like,
can I get one more copy?
And she learned a reading, and I did a reading,
and she's like, I love that.
And then she like, then she donated like twice that day,
you know, thanking for the reading, you know?
And he's hiding this person, I mean it's like and then I looked at my high like law class
He had hit 60 people like there's like a hundred people on there
I had to unhide at least 60 of them that I just didn't like
Right, I hit them and that's like
Because like no one was talking I was like why is there like a like 60 people in chat and no one's talking
And, yeah, there was, it was just, yeah, and I-
You bummed it all of them.
Yeah.
And so Alex cannot be a mod anymore,
but you guys, I will say, unless you really badly
behaving in the chat, please don't time out or hide Alex.
You know, this-
It's like, that's why I contacted you
and then I even joined to tell you what I did.
What happened?
Like, I got that one guy, I'm not gonna repeat it now
because it ended up breaking TLS, but that's why I did it.
Okay. Nancy was there too.
Okay, I mean, wow, it's it's just
Well, if you post the link now, we're gonna have at least two or four people come up
I'm gonna pin it real quick
Yeah, I'm gonna pin it
Apollo you heard
What
Copy cat will go stop being a good copy cat
My copy and I think I'm a little got a little bit distracted. I'm gonna pin the link
No, my copy
I've been saying that's like last year. Who am I copy? I think Sam Man says that now
Okay
In the link and then we crash out you crash on Alex okay crash on Alex when he gets up here
Cuz I have to take care of a little crisis, but I'll be right back and then a well fun
But here I'll be here to put him up. I just have to like
Link and I'll be right here. I mean, I just have I just have I'm kind of all just be right here. You're scared of me
Me now I'm not biting. Come on. I'm not biting. It's okay
Okay
Anybody's welcome up now if you'd like to come up pin
And
sleep
I sleep
Yeah, well, you got a new shape on your sheet, but you heard my sheet
I know you gotta
Can you stop saying this you heard shit man. This is a morning. I could stop boy
I don't think I'm gonna stop. Is there a problem with me saying that? Jesus
You're fine here
He just likes I mean he just this was this thing. I'd you know what?
You know what, I won't say any more, my bad.
I'm sorry.
Check that your microphone is on, it's on medium, Alex, please.
Thank you so much.
Hello.
I have five devices, with a hundred accounts on each.
That's five hundred accounts there, so you don't want that type of arming, I mean.
So don't touch my mic again, or I'm going to come in here with five hundred.
Come on Alex
Alex first of all you listen to me, okay Alex, you're not a mod. Okay, you're a chatter. Okay, you don't get special privileges
If you continue on this route Alex, I'm gonna find you again before I let you back up. Okay, Alex
I will let you have one more time you put right now
Alex listens to me right now
You put your microphone on half, okay?
If it's not half.
You watch your phone.
Yeah, and if it's not half, I'm just gonna kick you off and it'll be 50 bucks, okay?
That's gonna be it.
Okay?
If you don't pay 50 bucks, you're done.
Is my microphone okay or am I too loud?
You're fine. No, you're fine. It was it's Alex
Or ringing okay Alex don't disrespect me on my panel like this on my own show Alex. Don't do it again
Yeah, you should be permanently banned you didn't fuck the money you should be permanently banned
It's about to be but it's like I'm gonna give him another chance, but Alex you're my friend
I do
Have a show when you take you walk out all over me and I looked I looked like
And I like talking to you brother
Please don't like that. Don't be that fucking again. Okay. I'll let you back up in one minute. Okay. Don't you fucking do that again, Alex?
Okay, it's my show not your show. I would never
Like that, Alex. I don't care how many alts you have you're never getting back up here again if you do that again
Okay, you're in big trouble. Okay
Und ich weiß nicht, wie gut wir Freunde sind. Wir können vielleicht nur auf dem Telefon reden.
Dude, Alex, komm schon, dude, were you drunk?
Just stop, dude.
Pissing me off, Alex. I'm not in the mood right now, okay?
Oh, Saki's been a crash out for the first time ever.
We've seen a crash out.
Okay, listen, ich möchte, ich möchte, dass Hanna online kommt.
Ich möchte ein Gespräch mit Hanna, Hanna X spielen.
Go
My like like seriously
You don't want to get my mom. Yeah, you said that side of me is about to come out
Alex do not okay. No
I'm not gonna put up with that ever again. I think you're asking I don't think you're asking for too much here
I think that's a fair ass. I asked him before he came and he couldn't do one request and then he's like gonna threaten me
You're all and you're not gonna get up here tonight Alex
You better apologize to me in the chat Alex or just don't even bother. I'm just like I'm really
I was gonna be in a good mood with you, but I'm not I'm not playing not fucking playing
I mean, you know what? Maybe it's me. Maybe I make Alex act up. You know Alex
Guarantee I'll pay the fine because I know you're not gonna pay it
I think it's like 40 bucks now if I act out of pocket when you're up here
I'll pay the fine
But if you if you promise to come up here with your volume lower and you don't yell and you actually be cool
We can even debate anything like that for the longest you be cool
I'll literally pay it for you. I act stupid, but if you ask stupid brother, you have to go in your band
But if I ask stupid, I'll pay the fine
There you go. I think that's fair. I think I'm being I think I think that's good faith
Okay, I'm being really corny. I'm gonna bring him up now. Okay. We're gonna see what they would have
Alex if you okay, you're just already said Alex
You're on the air you gotta meet yourself my brother
He's muted so I don't fix the mic. That's why he's muted and then he's waiting to like come on
So what a hundred
On audio
No, I said
I said put it on the adjust
50% is a hundred because the top is 200
OK, well, that's why I'm a good year with the right in the middle when you push auto adjust
It's gonna be right in the middle. That's how it is
But I don't like it or just cuz all right just means I'm not adjusting it means some you or some moron or some computers adjusting it
I like to control my mic and I'll meet you halfway, bro. Just tell me what sounds good. I don't want to break everybody
I'm playing I'm out halfway. Okay
You're fine right now. It's halfway a hundred. This is where the question comes in because to me halfway's a hundred to you
Halfway of a thousand sir
It wouldn't be a hundred, would it?
I
You're patting off Alex
You hear the words
Alex news your tricks is getting upset and I'm getting upset because he knows I'm getting upset stop it
I'll turn a crash out
Yeah, we go
Alex get back in the bed. Go back to the bed Alex. We all we all still waiting for your crush out
We all still waiting for your crush out
Sorry
What a beautiful fucking cat
Thank you so I have one just like that but
She has like we're not even when she opens her mouth on her chin. It looks like she's saying oh
Like she's always shocked. Her name's Oreo
And then I have one that's it's I should have called her Reese's PCs
Because she has all those colors in here, but I call it cookie. She's like brown. She's like brown and I'm like a little bit
No, no dog be called mutt, but it's a cat
Oh
Like it's not what they call dogs when they're like
You can make a lot of money breeding dogs, brother. Like if they're like
Look at this electrosolverization
You're being generous elect, I think it wouldn't both like
This you won't talk to me I want my remix I think we were having that fun this weekend
Okay, we will have a fun weekend guys. We're gonna have fun weekends. Okay. Hey, baby
I love you. It should be weak might as well celebrate the weekend. I mean
I don't think there's any argument against that.
Might as well celebrate the weekend.
Let's do it.
Ooh.
You know what we're gonna do?
Oh my gosh.
We're gonna open up the fucking panel
and we're all gonna have a good time.
Okay, sounds like a plan.
And I don't wanna, yeah, I don't wanna book in.
I'm I had enough hard time
It was a really stressful week. It was a really stressful week. You guys can go see I did crash out
You know, I did the other day
I was screaming about biscuits in my chat for like five minutes and like I was like screaming at the top of my lungs about biscuit
I was so mad. I was so mad because some stuff came to light
He goes guess what I'm just asking of course. Yeah, go ahead
Taste the biscuit
Mother fucker
Jesus this biscuit shit is all
It's like it's like the stupidest meme it's like it's like the stupidest word
It's a stupidest reason for a fight, but you know what?
that's that's the way it all comes down to an AI song, especially that's the little song
here's the thing about getting older though
it's like a cute song, I still like it, it's like
yeah, but it makes you feel sometimes in life
the worst thing that the song ever did was that man
the biscuit was a little bit dry
I've learned and I've tried to tell you but I'm not smart
I'm fucking dumb, I know I'm dumb
I know I'm retired. I know I'm in no shit channel.
I can't pay you back to debate. That's what I learned about was like debate, like, especially with these pianos.
No shit channel.
Yeah, go ahead. Sorry, sorry. Go ahead.
Yeah, I'll leave it to you.
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Prado special weekend this weekend
We are I promise you that for like two weeks now. I guarantee I'm gonna keep my promise
Here we go guys. Oh, I think I have it here. I think this is it 200 bucks for psyche. Oh
I love you. This is the best listen
Apollo you're invited sir
This is no pink. It's he called the ghost
I'm calling it ghost tober. Okay. Here you go. Oh, I like it. I like it
Yeah, I swore a lot true
That's it offset psyche. I'm just me not that dude
Dude, this one or the other one?
It's already playing on the play, brother.
Fuck it, I'm proud of this one.
Ten bucks over the channel right now. Let's do it.
You down?
I only got about an hour and a half, thank you maybe, before I have to get back.
Time to open the can.
And I want some of the moderators to come by.
Talk about that a little bit.
You're still so loud got that big bro style got that easy sway if I had to choose you'd be here
And your quick firemind
From the late night chaos to the morning light
You've been here holding it down just right
If there's a hall of fame for the real and true
I'd carve your name in gold ghost
That's you
I won't forget you
You made me laugh till my face turns blue
You know you do
You're funny as hell, yeah
It's always a blast
These moments we're making
Are built to last
Thank you, ghost
You're one of a kind
With your big heart it mischief and you're quick
There we go, he got his wish.
Take this song, anyone want a song about them?
I can work it out.
Let me see.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Thank you, ghost.
Thank you so much, ghost.
I love you.
that's what I was going to say
I don't hate
I dislike for all these years I've been on these panels
when I'm
when I come up just now and you're like Alex
like you expect me to be sucking the phones
okay
I don't know if it's gonna work out
I mean I can just already tell
already tell it's gonna be a problem
I mean it's like Alex
Alex maybe it's better to like
Go to like beat his show or no, she doesn't let you on or something. Oh, she's like come on. Come on. No, please come on
Oh, no, no, I mean, it's like I mean, I don't know if he's loud anywhere. That's I'm I think am I the only show he's allowed
And he was always like that always like this, I mean, he's I think he's like
it's not even
the
Um, it goes this up to you whether you want him up here
Who Alex? Yeah, let him up here as long as he's such a fuck up put his volume up fucking
Possible to rain in years. It's just too difficult impossible to rain in Alex. Will you please prove these people wrong and rain in?
You got to unmute yourself, sir
Yeah
Oh, no robot it out. I'll give you a chance
Alex you sound like a robot
You're a robot Alex. Maybe that explains everything is a robot
Shut the fuck up man. That's you doing it. So
I'm not doing shit
Psyche
Let me check the chat
What would you like? Um, um, I want DJ Electra to join or a page. She feels like it. I mean, yeah, anybody that feels like it
Let me check the chat though. I haven't checked it for a while. No
I mean, it's just like I like this is this I like this hammer guy to join how my eggs
Yeah, come on up here. Can you join? Yeah
But I think I want to I think she wanted to because the chat was a little bit trollish, but I think or there's so many
Guess what you're getting Saturday you're getting 180 bucks
Different languages come on Hannah I
Somebody join I mean you're watching might as well join
You know what I think if I think I actually hurt you, you know, like I help you out
So many times like when you're in a debate, but if you're not in a debate like I hurt you because they don't want to fucking debate me
Me so I'm like a like it's like a good thing, but a bad thing, you know I'm saying
Well, you can debate me. I mean I
The people that hate you like it's a good thing I'm here, but the bad thing for me because like I stick up for you
But it's a good thing for me because I literally live for this shit. I literally love to argue well good
I mean I remember the first time
Don't laugh at it. I'm literally telling you the truth. I literally love to argue. I know you do
Like my bitch enough my girl
On the panel verse get um
get timed out for like five minutes and was on summer show when you were just like pissing everybody off on our show and someone timed you up for five minutes for five dollars.
I've been doing the same shit for a long time.
The rest is history guys.
The rest is history.
Shout out to Tony.
He is the man.
I just got a really good deal though. You know I have this um I have my um
I
Want to go to McDonald's. Oh
Hey, it goes. If you want McDonald's I can
You would be the kind of person that would give me my money back
Right now it's like that's like I got a serious question for you. Yes
By the way, I'm only giving you 180 this Saturday that you know goes
But whatever happens fish tacos brother, they shot maybe I'll go to the pier this weekend. Maybe it's I got a time for
Fuck it. You know what if you go
Fuck it. Keep the 20. I'll still give you we agreed. Well, we didn't agree
But I said I was gonna you know, we have some fun Saturday. I'll see you some money
But you keep the money, get some fish tacos brother.
I think that's good.
And you used to stream it too by the way.
You know what I had for dinner when I went with Alexandra?
You know what I had for dinner at the restaurant?
Hey, Barry and I have been in shrimp tacos
come and fight you if it was.
It was fish tacos.
Fish thigh and not sure
They're even kind of better than the peer
How was it though? How was the best fish? I think the best fish chopper that ever had
You're awesome. They were really really good and she had a skirt steak, you know
I think she's probably she likes you know what she likes. She likes lamb. She loves lamb
I love lamb soup, but um, I don't know if they had lamb with that
Lamb sheep or am I it's yes, it's a baby sheep
Don't say baby sheep
Is it a baby Apollo or is it the given lamb isn't a young one?
After a year. Yeah
Don't eat me it's bad
I'm sorry. I was a bad joke.
I'm so sorry. You know what?
I feel really, that hurt me.
What if it, well, you okay?
One time I ordered a deal at a restaurant.
Like my mom gave me the one time I ordered.
No, fuck it. Listen to me.
One time I ordered chicken McNuggets.
I didn't think it was chicken babies.
Yeah.
Well,
Chicken McNuggets, is it chicken baby? I thought it was chicken testicles
About huge chickens. It's like a large chicken testicles. That's what chicken nuggets are. No
Often every night it was a bad joke. It's just
I want my money back
It's all I got a 20 bucks to give Apollo I can get that shit for free
I
Love you guys. I love you guys we're having fun tonight. I'm getting a little bit both
But you know what I think the problem is me also as well because everyone thinks I always try to debate
I don't always try to debate what?
I do love the debate
Goes you know, it's really funny. So I go on I go on tiktok and it's like
But guess what you guys don't come to movie nights you guys only fucking let me join when I'm trying to
Think I'm a troll you guys look into this so tonight. I was
Yeah, we don't think you're troll dude. Oh, no, okay. No, no one thinks I am right no one thing there
I'm actually a master troll, but I'm not I don't do it on YouTube. I troll on tiktok
I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I
I think, uh, Electra is backstage, I hope so, because Apollo, you're fucking, you just
like, you just like, nine, or you just like, what, what, what, what did you say, what did
you say about me, what's your words, motherfucker, nine, so, young man, step down, okay, nine.
Bitch, I'll say it again. What's your problem with that? I'll say it again. You got a problem with it
You wanted to break you wanted to make a big name
I'm gonna ask your teeth. You're you will you gonna call it boy?
You're busy
You're a busy body boy, that's all what you are
You talk like you talking to like a like a racer. No one knows
If you ever wonder me, I'm down third of all, I'm pretty sure cycle be okay with it, but it's getting late
But no, no, no, no, no, I'm not down. I'm not down. No
So maybe you should set back shut the fuck up and just be cool. I don't want to debate you
I have nothing against you. Is that okay for me to get him out?
You're lost all the debate against me. Remember the score is
Never won against me you always lose against me
We all hang out you always to the to the elf you are loser debating me so shut the fuck up
learn English and then come back, okay?
Yes
Improve that the burden of proof is on you. Let's go sir
I can count losing my brain sense with these idiots.
I don't remember the last time I talked to you.
I guarantee I didn't lose to you, but go ahead and prove it.
I guarantee the meat would be rotten.
No, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
The vegetables.
Oh, finally.
I'm sorry, I didn't go to the bathroom.
I didn't go to the bathroom, sorry.
That's okay, that's all right.
I just went back in like 20 minutes.
You didn't even make the pee, you know?
Just kidding, I wasn't back in that one.
Look, electricity or ghosts, you're the way you are.
I was in a crowd, don't look.
Good go see how you did let your on the bitch here and let me go
Baiting about I debated before
What did that mean?
Hi sweetheart, how are you tonight?
Good, good, how are you?
Yeah, look at DC Tricks.
Who's this?
Elector, are you ready for the Saturday?
I love you, Elector.
Elector, are you ready?
What is Saturday? Like, what's happening?
Yeah, we're having a celebration.
Ghost is providing a very nice donation and awesome. Yeah
In there, I mean, I'm not rich or nothing. I'm putting it like I'll put like a penny in there
You know like from you guys. I know a guy's I'll bring the Jello shots. Okay. No free the music
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, it's
it's a little mama cat. She's
mama. This is Trix's mom and
she's like, oh, that's Trix's
mom. Can I ask a DJ like
sure. Have you ever heard like
I got five on it? You know,
like that old song. But did you
hear when the DJ was it?
when he used it? Uh the director
of uh get out when he used it?
I got so fucking creepy. That's a good movie. That's a good movie. Ever seen get out. Yeah, you know, yeah, that's scary
It's horrifying. It's a second. I don't do good with scary
But yeah, get out
Me and psyche go half on a sack and they played it so fucking creepy
They make it all slow or something like I'm not saying you should do that for I'm not saying you should get it
I'm saying you should make something like where'd you come from? Where'd you go?
Katanango
Also came up with a good idea for a song today. So I'm gonna write that song
It's a what song in what beat?
You give good white trash a bad name
That's great. Hey, Electra. Did you see like, um, you know trip kick kind of clipped my uh
Troll side of the panel at the end of that video. Do you see that part?
I didn't see it. What did he or the very very end of this of that video like where it's like, um, you know
You know the troll side of the panel, right?
that song. Yes. Oh, yeah.
definitely. You said you were
you're watching like when I
played that the last video we
watched yesterday. Yeah, but I
was editing some stuff too. So
I'm kind of okay. I just want
to play a tiny little bit
because it was so good. It was
like, yeah, play it. It's like
real quick before you do that.
Obviously, you do that. You
know, I should do when they
call me Sykes Boy when I join
these panels, I should make
them play my song. Yeah. Well,
this weekend, you can do that.
This is the very very this is like
This of this video I'll put it real quick. Hold on a second. Here we go. So this is like just like how they look how you how you
Here we go, it's right here
Here we go
I'm dancing to it against me good handsome guy
I can't hear shit.
You got me feeling muted.
I'm about to get booted.
I'm so overcomputed.
Can I work it out with anybody?
Play the code song.
We already played it.
All I want is chaos at its best.
Do you see this?
That was okay.
I'll play the game.
Oh my god, I love that.
I can't hear shit, guys.
it's okay. Do you want to play the other version of the ghost song ghost or no?
I can barely hear. I can hear you a little bit.
Can you hear me? Can you hear me? Hold on.
Do you want me to play the other version of the ghost song ghost?
Oh!
The elder verse? The elder verse I think is where like it was part of the panel
verse where there's kind of like more.
Okay, let's run it. I'm gonna run it anyway.
Yeah. Okay, I mean the ghost to make it fair I'm going to play the
Ladies first
Have a handy I want to play
Yes a handy hand I want a handy
If you haven't heard it it's called precious it called prep my precious friend here we go
In the static of the night, you light up the air
A spark in the silence, so be on compare
Kind heart shining, steady and true
He's got you more than a lot of you.
I'm sorry, I didn't hear my thoughts like this.
Well, I'm gonna get going if you guys come over.
What's we're gonna do on the Weepo film?
Yo, fuck what are you doing, dude, man?
Good song. That's awesome. I liked it. I liked it. That was awesome. I loved it.
That was one of those...Tammy's just kind of like Sia or something. Let me see if I can get...
Yeah, like Sia or maybe even Lady Gaga a little bit.
Yeah. Okay, I'll get Ghost Part 2. Let me see.
Where did Apollo go?
Uh-oh, I think...
Let's look at it when you play Ghost...
Here's the Ghost Part 2. Hold on. I'll play it real quick. Just so you're happy.
One second here you go
Get to get on camera and and dance for a gaudy can't end up with ghost picture. I'm just kidding. Yeah, hold on one second. Here we go
Yeah, I swore it was true
You laughed it off said psyche. I'm just me not that you
Oh my god
and you're quick fire my
You crack the whole panel you keep it alive
dropping jokes in the middle of the late night vibe
You're the spark in the storm. You're the wink in the crowd
Even when you're quiet you're still so loud got that big
DJ, can you jam to a little bit?
Yeah.
Can you move to the left?
Nope, no shit.
I don't care.
I don't like it, I don't like it.
and your quick fire my not Tony huh all right ghost i believe you
maybe
oh i was playing guitar why does it look like i'm scratching my vagina
don't play to us
why are you playing shit
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
Um, I don't know what else do I get is there any options? Um, you can get you can get a foot massage from me
Anything that has so is there anything that has to do with the open panel because people are gonna hate me if I don't say that
Um, what you can decide if Alice comes up you can have Alex control. I'll give you the Alps
That's that's good some power
Long to you though, so that's not fair
Alice to come up. Okay. You I mean, oh, we don't run into so long as I can go ahead. What do you want?
Who do you want? Just uh, you know
So you said open panel. Okay ghost. Where do you which word do you want to first of all?
I'm gonna make the banner say thank you ghost. Okay. Where do you want to be on which which square do you want to be in?
The top left top right bottom right or bottom left you get to choose. Don't call me a bottom, please
Okay, you could be you can be on top. Okay. Hold on. They're gonna
Stop right you heard
There you go
Oh, you want to talk to you wanted me next selector there you go
There you go. I don't want to be I don't want to be underneath her. I mean
Okay, well, it's not gonna be like Adam and Lilith. It's gonna be Electra and Ghosts
Okay, you don't have to fight about it
Listen to me though, I feel like I need one card
Okay, you want a card? Okay, the animal card. You love the animal card. I can do the animal card. No, I don't feel like it's an animal card.
You gave me the death card by the way just pointing that out
That's okay. I mean that you will according to Shannon it means, you know on to new things
But I say maybe do this thing behind but okay. Here's the animal part of pull animal part for you
I will pull one for everybody on the panel
No, I'm shuffling I'll shuffle until you say stop just someone's up
All right, go ahead that one. Okay. Yeah, you got yeah, you got the polar bear you got the polar bear
It's like I think his name is non-nukes. Yeah, I am a bear and she can hibernate with me anytime she wants you
It says polar bear symbol of the power wisdom and peace
In a way, people consider the polar bear, which they call Nunuuk, to be powerful in
the world.
The legend of Kukki-ki-ok describes a ten-legged polar bear.
Living in the Arctic Islands of his four-legged relatives and attempted to create a community based on peace and love in this painting
Titled playing with the north wind
Kind of like the ghosts right the bear dancing in cavoars with the wind
Boulay who identified
Fourpaw, the bear, and the painting appears to be saying goodbye, but that's just Boulay saying goodbye because you know Boulay passed away a year later
But yeah, that's not new to Polar Bear
But there's the there's the ghosts the wind is the ghost kind of like a ghost. I like that, right?
Okay, so who's next?
Apollo or Electra is next
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You have the bear you got the bear. Oh, and you got the bear there's a bear and it said
Symbols of healing, divinity, and invulnerability.
The bear is full as divinity and healing in many cultures.
The Ainu people of the Northern Islands of Japan
believe the bear was a mountain god.
In India, bears are believed to prevent disease.
Children may ride on a bear's back to avoid sickness.
And among the Pheno-Ugric peoples,
he was the god of heaven.
The bear has bigger prominently in Native American people
who regarded it as a spirit.
Spirit. What's that? Helper. The painting of the bear woman dancing with a rattle recalls the Pawnee Indian story of bear medicine woman in which a girl born with a bear spirit has the power to heal. Okay?
So maybe they got a great healing power and you know divinity and it's like a very special animal for the bear. Okay?
And now in the lecture. So, Electra, tell me when to stop. Okay?
Okay.
And you got the Fox.
You are a Fox.
In the wild, it exists in the edges of fields and forests in the mythical realm is a principal mediator between that human and spirit worlds.
In Chinese folklore, the fox may assume a human shape at the age of 50.
At its 100th birthday, it becomes either a wizard or a lovely maiden.
Red foxes are associated with sexual energy and the creative life force.
Some Native American legends speak of a hunter discovering that his wife has a secret fox identity.
I was just trying to debate with my dude psyche. I think I found you. You got me? Oh, yeah, you did. You got me? Where?
Let me see. Do you want me to pull a car for myself?
Yes.
There you go.
Okay, and I'll pull one for chat too.
You almost went animal chatter.
I'm going to pull one for me because
God is leading me right to you, girl.
Aww.
I think it goes to the crash.
I don't disrespect you. I got I got the Heron. I got the Heron the bird.
Yeah, because it was seen in flight over the fields when the Nile began to flood it was associated with fertility and the renewal of life
In the roman epic the anus the heron is to get a symbol of renewal
And it's depicted rising from the ashes of the burn city of ar'dia. So it's like kind of like the phoenix
I like that and I feel like I feel like I haven't gone through a I think I
Yes
Well, you said there's that's not a debate. You know, it's a tarot card reading channel, right?
Yeah, okay, so what?
It's a panel first question. Go ahead. Yeah, number channel to
Well, listen, I would like to shout out to ladies reading here, and I think it's very brave for you guys to be here
And like don't be rude when like if I say anything and you guys like leave because I'm rude because I am a piece of shit
I do love the bloods. I do love debating. I do love blood sports
Oh my god, yeah, okay. Okay. It goes to an Alex fucking apologize, bitch. You're not gonna
apologize. Are you? You're talking about German, big ass fucking German accent. What you don't know where the fuck
you're from. Let's go to Alex or kick him from the studio. You don't know where the fuck you're from,
German. Where are you from, actually?
He's voting Greece, and he lives in Germany
Do is you're gonna sit there and be a good boy, huh?
You don't fuck
Pull the car to Amanda can you do Amanda?
Christine
Goes okay, Amanda you got the wolf card, okay, Amanda
It says, symbolism, creation, healing, and purification.
Although portrayed as a marauding villain in many European cultures, wolves are deities
in Native American cosmologies and are popular to people like the raven, which also appears
in the painting.
Where's the raven?
Somewhere in the
Raven and the wolf is a hero and creator in some legends
She is the trickster sibling of the coyote
the
Quillette in the macaw of the Pacific Northwest ascribe healing power to the wolf and perform a wolf dance in the skin of the animal to
Cure the sick in the early Roman cult of lupa or pharonia
The great she-wolf also known as the mother of wolves was the divine midwife and matriarch of the ancestors
annual festival and so the she-wolf will vote in purification rituals the Roman legend of Romulus and Remus
A wolf nurses the two heroes and restores their strength
Here we go
Well, it did say alpha I mean the wolf yeah, maybe it is a
I don't see Alpha anymore in the thing. Let me see. No, it doesn't say Alpha anymore
Lupa or Feronia, I'd say answer. No, I don't see Alpha
Yeah, but it's beautiful card though, and it's uh, yeah
It's a creation healing
Okay, I'm Alex do it Alex up here. No
I'll take a little piece if you guys don't mind. Okay, let's do it
Raise yourselves. I really like just like to hang out and talk, but I'll take it over you. Okay. I'll make it
I'll put myself up in the middle
Let's run it
You want to be on top too? Okay, there you go
perfect
Let's run it feeling good Amanda and I said how much it does how much to
But to you how much to but to you Alex says what do we know it's
No, how much to buy you because I would be ghost boy you bro. This is ghost's panel
Information bro, what's going on? What did I miss in two days?
That's not
I literally paid to have you up here. You're not a lot up here, brother
You just break I guess you're too much. I literally paid to have you up here. I
Mean, I would
Okay, who do we have back here? Oh, you have a song a picture of my cat
That's mr. Cute
What's up
He's gone. I'm Alex. I kicked him out of the studio.
He's not in the studio.
Says they had to change the demand due to
Atlas, the alien mothership headed to Earth.
Spanky knows some stuff.
Spanky, why are you in the ban list?
I noticed I unbanned you
because I didn't quite remember what you did.
Did you do something that I don't remember?
But hopefully you're a cool person.
I just remember Spanky,
some people like you're spunky and stuff,
but so Nancy means so, oh yeah.
And it says, Shannon says,
Cute character. Oh, that's a cute character. Gaudi. Is Gaudi here? Why are you on that name?
Is Gaudi, what is his name? Oh, it's Spanky. Gaudi, I get it.
That's not Gaudi, okay. I don't know. Hey, Shan, what's up? You know what the funny thing is,
uh, Psych, I would never agree with him, but I'm literally like, I love to debate so much. I could
Yeah, he's just so annoying right now. I mean, it's
I don't want to get I don't he's getting personal and it's like, you know, whatever
What do you want it to be?
ghost
Uh, are you gonna? Uh, well, here's my one question. I this is actually a road debate. Are you gonna be ready by uh this weekend?
uh-huh
We mixed that what I told you about
Yeah, I started
Well, bitch, we got next week and we're gonna go I
know but I had to
Take the vocals out and then redo the vocals and then I have to slow it down or speed it up
I'm not sure which way to go yet and put some
You're gonna handle this there's a radio DJ. I didn't actually do music. I just started doing music
I love mystery and I like
What's the other the rock song?
Yeah
Her name is DJ Electra DJ
You literally wait until we only have like 24 hours to do it and then you said you're not the real DJ
Okay, we have a guest. We have a guest on hold. Uh-oh. Oh shit. I can't have them on because of mine.
Okay, I have to end the show and then restart because if I have this person on
No, I know but if I had the verse on he's gonna get my the show taken down
So I need to like restart it so he can come up because I've been a
Reviler, Rewriter Red
and he's kind of kind of so come back in like two minutes or just everybody just come shuffle
back i'll have it in two minutes okay just okay okay it'll just be i'll just end it real quick
and then i'll be right there okay here we go